J. J. McCullough
...as a result, ice cream has evolved
into a pretty unique consumer good,
in the sense that customers are
allowed (or even encouraged) to have
pretty idiosyncratic preferences,
that the industry is nevertheless
happy to cater to.
But in any case, according to a
2017 study by the IDFA,
America's leading Dairy Industry
lobby group,
the five best-selling American
Ice Cream flavors these days are:
...and Chocolate Chip Cookie Dough.
A 2020 YouGov poll by the American
public, meanwhile, yielded basically
the same results,
with the only difference being that
in their list, they also had
...and...
..."pee-can."
"Pee-cans" are another plant that is
indigenous to North America.
According to this book about
the history of "pee-cans,"
early European settlers tended to
dismiss "pee-cans" as being basically
the same as walnuts,
which they already had in Europe,
so who cares.
To this day, America produces over
80% of the world's "pee-cans,"
and they're mostly just eaten
by Americans.
Joey
You make great videos, J.J.
You were so close.
I'm sorry, J.J.
You made me do this.
This is a pecan.
This is a dish of pecans.
These are NOT...
..."PEE-CANS!"
THIS... is a "Pea-Can."
This is also a "Pee-Can."
*sounds of sloshing liquid*
Yes, I urinated in this can
just to make this point.
Now, let me be completely clear.
This is not an opinion.
This is not an argument.
"Puh-kaanz" is an OBJECTIVELY
better pronunciation,
because "Pee-cans" sounds
D I S G U S T I N G !
And pecans don't deserve a
disgusting conotation.
After all, they're delicious!
Don't you agree?